Guide to the Stanford University, Queer Student Resources, Records SC0252
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Queer Student Resources, records
1972-2016
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Gay People's Union (Stanford, Calif.).
Gay Community of Concern.
Stanford University. Stanford Women's Collective
Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford
Koskovich, Gerard
Stanford University. The Bridge
Whitman-Radclyffe Foundation
Stanford University. LGBT Community Resources Center
SC0252
61.5 Linear Feet (18 cartons, 46 boxes, 5 half boxes, 5 flat boxes)
Collection consists of the records of the LGBT Community Resources Center and its predecessors the Gay People's Union (GPU), and the Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford (GLAS). Included are correspondence, memoranda, office files, reference files on service organizations in Santa Clara and San Mateo Counties, log books, notebooks, questionnaires, tape recordings, videos, photographs, posters, and ephemera pertaining to the gay, lesbian, and transgender community at Stanford and the surrounding communities.
Arrangement note
The materials are arranged by accession.
Separated Materials
Issues of Vector magazine were removed and individually cataloged as part of the Stanford University Libraries Special Collections' rare books and manuscripts collections, call number HQ75 .V43.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Administrative transfers, 1981-2016.
Information about Access
Three boxes in the GPU/GLAS Records series are restricted in accordance with donor agreement. The files will remain closed until January 1, 2060 (75 years after last date of creation). Otherwise the collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Description of the Collection
Collection consists of the records of the LGBT Community Resources Center and its predecessors GLAS (Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford) and the Gay People's Union. Included are correspondence, memoranda, office files, reference files on service organizations in Santa Clara and San Mateo Counties, log books, notebooks, VECTOR magazine, questionnaires, tape recordings, videos, photographs, posters, and ephemera pertaining to the gay, lesbian, and transgender community at Stanford and the surrounding communities. Collection also includes the records of the Gay Community of Concern, 1974-1976, a local community group; records from the Women's Collective, 1974-85; and some materials concerning the Palo Alto School Board anti-discrimination policy, 1975. Tape recordings include "Gay Life Styles," 1975, and Leonard Matlovich speaking at Stanford, 1975.
Biographical / Historical
In 1971, a group of students, staff, and alumni came together to form the Gay People's Union at Stanford – one of the first LGBT campus organizations in America.
In 1984, Stanford Pride was established on an alumni group.
Queer Student Resources, formerly, LGBT Community Resources Center, is a student organization whose services include mentoring, diversity awareness, lecture series, support groups, workshops, and culture events. Programs represented in the records include the Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week, BGLAD (Bisexual, Gay, and Lesbian Awareness Days), AIDS Education Project, and Queer Awareness Days (QuAD).
Transsexual college students -- United States.; Transgenderism -- United States.; Lesbians.; Lesbian college students -- United States.; Memorabilia.; Gay college students -- United States.; Speeches.; Education, higher -- Social aspects -- United States.; Bisexual college students -- United States.; Homosexuality and education -- United States.; Gays; Peer counseling -- California.; Gay People's Union (Stanford, Calif.).; Gay Community of Concern.; Stanford University. Stanford Women's Collective; Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford; Stanford University. LGBT Community Resources Center; Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford; Koskovich, Gerard; Stanford University. The Bridge; Gay Community of Concern.; Whitman-Radclyffe Foundation; Stanford University. LGBT Community Resources Center; Whitman-Radclyffe Foundation; Gay People's Union (Stanford, Calif.).
- GPU/GLAS Records
  Biographical/Historical note
  In 1972, gay and lesbian students on the Stanford campus organized the Gay Person's Union (GPU) as a forum for open discussion of homosexuality, as a locus of political activity to promote Gay and Lesbian rights both at Stanford and the community at large, and as a safe environment for gay men and lesbians to socialize with one another. Around 1983, GPU changed its name to the Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford (GLAS) to emphasize that GPU was not intended as a males-only environment and that the involvement of women as members of the organization was vital.
  Over the years, GLAS became an umbrella organization under which numerous other gay and lesbian organizations on the Stanford campus operated. Most notable among these organizations within GLAS are the Women's Collective; the Gay and Lesbian Awareness (GALA) week committee, which organizes an annual GALA week activities that promote awareness and visibility of gay and lesbian students on the Stanford campus; and the Gay and Lesbian Speakers Bureau, which as part of the Residential Education policy of the University provided educational outreach to the dormitories and other residences by sending gay and lesbian students to speak about their personal experiences growing up, living at Stanford, etc.
  During the early 1970s, the Gay Community of Concern (GCC) also operated on the Stanford campus. While it was a "separate entity" from GPU, many of the members of GCC were also members of GPU. In exchange for the use of GPU office space, paid GCC staffers ran the GPU office on a quid pro quo basis. When the GCC disbanded in the Winter of 1977 due to the cessation of state and federal (CETA) grant monies, its records remained in the GPU offices.
  - Series I
    Access to Collection
    Some materials are restricted in accordance with donor agreement and will not be opened for use until 2060.
    Scope and Contents
    Records reflect the foundng of the Gay People's Union (GPU) in the early 1970s, which was the original name of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford (GLAS). Materials include office files of the GPU and GLAS from 1972-1985. Included within the general office records are the files on the various events and activities produced by GLAS as well as the records of some the organizations and committees that fell beneath the umbrella provided by GPU/GLAS. GPU materials include: log books, meeting notes, budgets, newsletters, correspondence, flyers, and items relating to Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week (GLAW). GLAS materials include: correspondence, budgets, speaker information, activism, events, scholarships, information about other gay organizations.
    - Gay People's Union - Log Book (1 of 3), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Gay People's Union - Log Book (2 of 3), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Gay People's Union - Log Book (3 of 3), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Gay People's Union - Meeting/Training Notes (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Gay People's Union - Meeting/Training Notes (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Gay People's Union - Meeting/Training Notes (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Gay People's Office Records - Constitution, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Gay People's Union - Miscellaneous Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Gay People's Union - Activities Log, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Gay People's Union - Phone Log, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Gay People's Union - Budget and Misc., 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Gay People's Union - ASSU Student Organization Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Gay People's Union - ASSU Student Organization Fund, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Gay People's Union - ASSU Student Organization Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Gay People's Union - Budget, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Gay People's Union - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Gay People's Union - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gay People's Union - Budget: Bookkeeping Ledger, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - HEW - Office of Education - "Help Communities Help Themselves", circa 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Orientation, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - "The Realities of Homosexuality" (Lecture), 1974 Mar 9 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Conference and Gay Pride Week, 1974 Jun (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Career Planning and Placement Center - Non-Discrimination Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - GPU - Conference: Evaluation Forms, 1974 Jun (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Gay Freedom Celebration (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - GPU Newsletter, Financial Data, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - GPU Newsletter, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - GPU - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - GPU Newsletter/Pub Board (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - GPU Office Log, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Stanford Libraries - GPU Donations, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - GPU Correspondence from Stanford, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Call Computer Co., 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Scholarship/Loan Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - GPU - Misc., 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - GPU Misc. Materials, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Stanford Libraries - Locked Stack Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Human Rights Policy Proposal, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Gay People's Union Newsletter - copies, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Non-discrimination policy: Documents from Stanford News and Publication files., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Gay Student Organizations, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - GPU - Misc. Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - GPU Steering Committee, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - California Campus Coalition for Gay/Lesbian Rights, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Disorientation Week, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Gay Freedom Day, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - "A Very Natural Thing" (film), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Brigg's Initiative, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Office of Student Activities, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - GPU Budget: Bookkeeping Ledger, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - GPU - ASSU, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Anti-discrimination policy - correspondence, proposals, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Orientation, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - GPU - Misc., 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Tea Room Raids, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Steering Committee - Agenda and Minutes, 1976; 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Internal Communications, 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - GPU - Directory Listings, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - GPU - ASSU Acct., 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - PACER/Palo Alto Equal Rights Ordinance, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - In. Commercial, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - In. Organizations, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Disorientation, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Hooverville '32/Reaganville '82 (Endorsed by GLAS), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Orientation, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Internal Communications, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - GPU Speakers Series, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - GPU - Work Study Staff Position, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Steering Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Parade, San Francisco, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - GLAW - Funding info and proposals, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Misc. old papers (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Financial Documentation, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Financial Documentation, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Advertisements (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - California Legislature - Gay Employment Rights Bill AB 1, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - California State Legislative SB 910 (AIDS Funding) (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - In. Commercial, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence In - Misc. Non-gay organizations. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Misc. correspondence - In., 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Misc. correspondence - Out., 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - GLAS speaking engagement - Donner Hall, 1983 Mar 31 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Cowell Student Health Center -- Hepatitis B Vaccine, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Directory listings, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - GLAS events and activities, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - GPU/GLAS events and activities -- dances, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - GLAS events and activities - Ski trip, 1983 Feb 12-13 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Freedom of information requests - Federal Bureau of Investigation, National Headquarters, Washington DC, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Freedom of information request - Federal Bureau of Investigation, San Francisco field office, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Freedom of information request - SF FBI - advocate article, misc. memos & correspondence, clippings re Stanford., 1982 Oct-Nov (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Freedom of Information Act request - appeals process, 1982- (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Gay Games II, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - GLAS questionnaire, 1982 fall (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - GLAS scholarship -- correspondence, press releases, internal communications., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - GLAS scholarship -- donations: correspondence and accounts., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Gay scholarship press clippings, 1983 Feb (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - GLAS speaking engagement - Loro Hall, 1983 Apr 7 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Internal communications, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - G.L.A.S. library (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Office calendar, 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Orientation, 1982 fall (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Stanford - Office of Student Activities, 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Posters (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Robert Ragland - scholarship offer and general correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Newsletter, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Publicity (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Stanford - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU) - Misc., 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Steering Committee - agendas & minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - T-shirt info (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Western Regional Lesbian and Gay Student Conference [CSU Sacramento], 1983 Mar 11-13 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - In (organizations), 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - In, Commercial, 1983- (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - In, general, 1983- (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - In, general: John Golden/David Ostafin (University of Connecticut) student survey (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - In, organizations - separate headings, 1983- (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Steering Committee - minutes, agendas, misc. materials (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - In - Misc. Gay/Lesbian organizations, 1983- (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - In - Misc. Gay/Lesbian student organizations (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - In - misc. non-gay organizations, 1983- (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Events (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - In, Personal: Ken Weedin, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - Out, 1983- (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - D. Bernard (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - ASSU check stubs (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Ms. advertisements from GLAS bulletin boards, 1983- (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Directory listings (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Financial reports, 1983- (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - GLAS events and activities - proposed, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - GLAS events and activities, 1983- (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - GLAS events and activities - Dances, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - GLAS events and activities - Tom Wilson-Weinberg, 1984 Feb 29 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - GLAS events and activities - Brongersma talk on pedophilia, 1984 Mar 8 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - GLAS events and activities - Edouard Roditi poetry reading, 1984 Apr 12 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Internal communications, 1983- (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - "In The News" bulletin board - misc. clippings (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Letterhead designs - proposed, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - GLAS library project (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - GLAS newsletter - vol.2, no.3, 1983 Dec (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - GLAS newsletter, 1984 Apr (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - GPU/GLAS posters and handbills, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - GLAS posters - defaced examples, 1983- (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - GPU/GLAS press releases, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Orientation (events and activities), 1983 fall (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Office calendar, 1983 Oct- (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Tape message (outgoing) -- Mss. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ASSU - General materials, 1983- (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - GLAS office records - financial records, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - California State Legislature - Assembly Bill 1, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - California State Legislature - Assembly Bill 848 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Coalition Aginst Olympic Homophobia (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Coalition Against Olympic Homophobia, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Maricopa County, Arizona. Board of Supervisors -- Hawley Atkinson Affair, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - National Gay Task Force -- Gay/Lesbian Student Organization support packet, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Media Relations - General, 1983- (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Gay youth feature for the Mercury News (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - National march for lesbian/gay rights, San Francisco, 1984 Jul 15 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Newsweek On Campus "Gay students" article (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Northern California lesbian and gay students (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Parents & friends of lesbians and gays (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Palo Alto NOW Lesbian Rights Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Peninsula Business Guild (Redwood City) (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - San Francisco Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Parade, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - San Jose Gay Pride celebration, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - George Segal's "Gay Liberation" - defacement - "Speak Out in White Plaza", 1984 Mar 12 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Segal's "Gay Liberation" - defacement - press releases and clippings, 1984 Mar 6- (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Segal - "Gay Liberation" - defacement - correspondence with Albert L. Gordon (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Segal - "Gay Liberation" - defacement of signs following vandalism - administrative response (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - George Segal's "Gay Liberation" - defacement - signs from site vandalism on ..., 1984 Mar 9 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - George Segal's "Gay Liberation" - defacement - signs from site vandalized on ..., 1984 Mar 12 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - George Segal's "Gay Liberation" - defacement - general documentation, internal communications, etc., 1984 Mar 10- (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - George Segal's "Gay Liberation" - General documentation, communications, etc. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Stanford: Cowell Student Health Center - Counselling and psychological services (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Daily - AIDS article, 1983 Oct 17 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Daily - AIDS and blood donation stories, 1984 Jan 30-Feb 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Stanford Daily - Valentines personal advertisements incident and business practices modification demand, 1984- (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Stanford Daily - "Once Around the Quad" listings (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Stanford University News Service - AIDS and blood donation story (and pickups), 1984 Jan 23 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Business Students Association (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Stanford - Gay and Lesbian Counselling Group at the Bridge - misc. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Law Students' Association, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Speakers Bureau, 1983- (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Stanford - Office of Student Activities, 1983- (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Stanford - University Events and Services (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Stanford Women's Center (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Dan White - release from jail - clippings, etc. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - GLAS office records - misc. records, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - About This Filing System (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Filing Records (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Agenda and minutes of Steering Committee meetings (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - The Steering Committee (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Financial affairs (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Financial records (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Financial affairs - ASSU account records, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Internal communication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Announcements at the men's social (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Internal communication - phone messages (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Phone numbers of various GLASsies, old and new (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Gay and lesbian resources at Stanford (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Calendar (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - The GLAS fridge (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Newsletter: fall 1984 - not published, 1984 fall (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Newsletter: fall 1984/winter 1985 - published, 1984 fall-1985 winter (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Internal communication - bulletin boards (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - GLAS library (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Housing ads (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Directory listings (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Events tape: scripts (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Posters defaced (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Archives project (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Proposed events and activities (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - General events and activities (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Open House, 1984 Oct 11 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Orientation, 1984 fall (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Dances (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - AIDS talk, 1984 Nov 13 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Jacques Vademborghe talk, 1984 Nov 29 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Consenting Adults", 1985 Feb 4 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous co-sponsored events and activities (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Interfaith commem. for holocaust victims, 1985 Apr 17 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Mid-Peninsula Civil Rights Forum (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "In the News" board - miscellaneous clippings (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Press releases (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Press statements (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - AIDS-related issues (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - HTLV-III testing (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Parade, S.F., 1985 Jun 30 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Parents & Friends of Lesbians & Gays - Mid-Peninsula (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - San Jose gay organizations (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - International March for Lesbian & Gay Freedom (New York) (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - "AM San Francisco" (ABC-TV), 1985 June 28 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Palo Alto G & L Community Council (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Gay & Lesbian student organizations - miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - ASSU (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Student organization services (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - RA Training Workshop on Gay/Lesbian Issues, 1985 Aug (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Stanford Students Opposed to Pornography (STOP) (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Stanford Progressive Alliance (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Rape Education Project (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Bisexuality Discussion Group (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Students Against Reaganism (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - "Stanford T-Shirt Museum" - Branner Hall, 1985 Mar 7 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Administration - Stanford (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - University Libraries (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Gay resource person, Stanford administration (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Alumni Association, Stanford (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Work Study Program (Federal) - Office of Financial Aids (Box 13, Folder 31)